Register of the Institute of Economic Affairs (Great Britain) records
Hoover Institution Archives
- Incremental Materials, 1947-2010
  - Publications File, 1987-1999
    - Manuscripts
      - General
        - Evans, Alan W., 1992 (Box-folder 440: 7)
        - Evans, Tim, 1993 (Box-folder 440: 8)
        - Foster, Robert and Alan Peacock, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 440: 9)
        - France, Virginia, 1995 (Box-folder 440: 10)
        - Glaister, Stephen, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 441: 1)
        - Greenaway, David, 1992 (Box-folder 441: 2)
        - Gwartney, James, 1996 (Box-folder 441: 3)
        - Hanson, Charles, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 441: 4)
        - Hartley, Keith, 1992 (Box-folder 441: 5)
        - Hague, Douglas, 1993 (Box-folder 441: 6)
        - Hindley, Brian, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 441: 7)
        - Hunter, Williams, 1993 (Box-folder 441: 8)
        - Jackman, Richard, 1991 (Box-folder 441: 9)
        - Jay, Antony, 1994-1996 (Box-folder 441: 10)
        - Kealey, Terence, 1992-1994 (Box-folder 441: 11)
        - Keating, Giles, 1991 (Box-folder 441: 12-13)
        - King, David, 1992 (Box-folder 441: 14-15)
        - Lal, Deepak, 1992-1995 (Box-folder 441: 16)
        - Lal, Deepak, 1994-1996 (Box-folder 442: 1-2)
        - McGee, Robert, 1992-1994 (Box-folder 442: 3)
        - McRae, Hamish, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 442: 4)
        - Marsh, Paul, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 442: 5)
        - Meltzer, Allan, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 442: 6)
        - Migue, Jean-Luc, 1994 (Box-folder 442: 7)
        - Miller, Robert and John B. Wood, 1993 (Box-folder 442: 8)
        - Minford, Patrick, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 442: 9)
        - Nieuwenhuysen, John, 1993 (Box-folder 442: 10)
        - O'Sullivan, Patrick and Nigel Allington, 1990-1992 (Box-folder 442: 11)
        - Parker, David and Stephen Martin, 1991-1993 (Box-folder 442: 12)
        - Pepper, Gordon, 1991 (Box-folder 442: 13)
        - Ponnuru, Ramesh, 1993-1995 (Box-folder 442: 14)
        - Powell, Jeffrey, 1992 (Box-folder 442: 15)
        - Rizzo, Ilde, 1993-1994, undated (Box-folder 443: 1)
        - Robinson, Colin, 1991 (Box-folder 443: 2)
        - Robinson, Gordon, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 443: 3)
        - Seldon, Arthur, 1989-1994 (Box-folder 443: 4-5)
        - Sachs, Jeffrey, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 443: 6)
          See Audiovisual Materials for cassette tape.
        - Scott, Maurice, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 443: 7)
        - Senior, Ian, 1995 (Box-folder 443: 8)
        - Simon, Julian, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 443: 9)
        - Smith, Fred, 1992 (Box-folder 443: 10)
        - Sorensen, Peter Birch, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 443: 11)
        - Spottiswoode, Clare, 1993 (Box-folder 443: 12)
        - Staley, Sam, 1992-1995 (Box-folder 443: 13)
        - Stroup, Richard, 1993 (Box-folder 443: 14)
        - Van Brabant, Jozef, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 443: 15)
        - Veljanovski, Cento, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 444: 1)
        - Walters, Alan, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 444: 2)
        - White, Lawrence H., 1995-1996 (Box-folder 444: 3)
        - Whitfield, Richard, 1995 (Box-folder 444: 4)
        - Wolf, Martin, 1992 (Box-folder 444: 5)
        - Wood, Geoffry and Lakis Kaounides, 1992 (Box-folder 444: 6)
        - Wood, Geoffrey E. (editor), 1995-1996 (Box-folder 444: 7)
        - Woolley, Paul, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 444: 8)
      - Current Controversies
        - #1, 1992 (Box-folder 444: 9)
        - #2, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 444: 10)
        - #3, 1992 (Box-folder 444: 11)
        - #4, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 444: 12)
        - #5, 1993 (Box-folder 444: 13)
        - #6, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 445: 1)
        - #7, 1993 (Box-folder 445: 2)
        - #8, 1994 (Box-folder 445: 3)
        - #9, 1994 (Box-folder 445: 4)
        - #10, 1994 (Box-folder 445: 5)
      - Education and Training Unit
        - #1, 1996 (Box-folder 445: 6)
        - #8, 1999 (Box-folder 445: 7)
      - Hobert Paperbacks
        - #30, 1990-1996 (Box-folder 446: 1)
        - #31, 1992 (Box-folder 446: 2)
        - #107, 1991-1995 (Box-folder 446: 3)
        - #112, 1996 (Box-folder 446: 4)
        - #114, 1996 (Box-folder 446: 5)
        - #115, 1989-1993 (Box-folder 446: 6)
        - #116, 1990-1992 (Box-folder 446: 7)
        - #117, 1991 (Box-folder 446: 8)
        - #118, 1991-1994 (Box-folder 446: 9)
        - #119, 1992 (Box-folder 446: 10)
        - #120, 1992-1994 (Box-folder 447: 1)
        - #121, 1991-1994 (Box-folder 447: 2-3)
        - #122, 1992-1996 (Box-folder 447: 4)
        - #123, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 447: 5)
        - #124, 1991-1997 (Box-folder 447: 6)
        - #125, 1993-1997 (Box-folder 448: 1-2)
        - #126, 1993-1997 (Box-folder 448: 3)
        - #127, 1991-1995 (Box-folder 448: 4-5)
        - #128, 1993-1995 (Box-folder 448: 6)
        - #129, 1992-1996 (Box-folder 449: 1)
        - #130, 1992-1996 (Box-folder 449: 2)
        - #134, 1994-1998 (Box-folder 449: 3)
      - Occasional Papers
        - #85, 1990-1993 (Box-folder 449: 4)
        - #86, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 449: 5)
        - #87, 1992 (Box-folder 449: 6)
        - #88, 1992-1994 (Box-folder 449: 7)
        - #89, 1993-1996 (Box-folder 449: 8)
        - #90, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 450: 1)
        - #91, 1993 (Box-folder 450: 2)
        - #92, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 450: 3)
        - #93, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 450: 4)
        - #94, 1994-1996 (Box-folder 450: 5)
        - #95, 1995 (Box-folder 450: 6)
        - #96, 1995 (Box-folder 450: 7)
        - #97, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 450: 8)
        - #98, 1996 (Box-folder 450: 9)
      - Readings
        - #40, 1992-1994 (Box-folder 451: 1)
        - #41, 1993-1995 (Box-folder 451: 2-3)
        - #42, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 451: 4-5)
        - #43, 1994-1996 (Box-folder 451: 6)
        - #43 (cont'd.), 1994-1996 (Box-folder 452: 1)
        - #46, 1987-1998 (Box-folder 452: 2)
        - #47, 1991-1994 (Box-folder 452: 3)
        - #48, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 452: 4)
        - #49, 1988-1994 (Box-folder 452: 5-6)
        - #49 (cont'd.), 1988-1994 (Box-folder 453: 1-2)
        - #50, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 453: 3-4)
        - #51, 1991-1995 (Box-folder 453: 5)
        - #52, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 453: 6)
      - Studies on the Environment
        - #1, 1994 (Box-folder 454: 1)
        - #2, 1994 (Box-folder 454: 2)
        - #3, 1995 (Box-folder 454: 3)
        - #4, 1995 (Box-folder 454: 4)
        - #5, 1995 (Box-folder 454: 5)
        - #6, 1996 (Box-folder 454: 6)
    - Rejected Publications
      - A, 1992-1996 (Box-folder 454: 7)
      - B, 1989-1992 (Box-folder 454: 8)
      - C, 1990-1993 (Box-folder 454: 9)
      - D-E, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 454: 10)
      - F, 1990-1995 (Box-folder 455: 1)
      - G, 1993-1995 (Box-folder 455: 2)
      - H-J, 1991-1994 (Box-folder 455: 3)
      - K, 1991-1996 (Box-folder 455: 4-5)
      - L, 1991-1994 (Box-folder 455: 6)
      - Mc, 1990-1995 (Box-folder 455: 7)
      - M, 1991-1995 (Box-folder 455: 8)
      - N, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 456: 1)
      - O, 1993 (Box-folder 456: 2)
      - P-Q, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 456: 3)
      - R, 1990-1993 (Box-folder 456: 4)
      - S, 1991-1996 (Box-folder 456: 5-6)
      - T, 1991-1993 (Box-folder 456: 7)
      - U-V, 1993-1996 (Box-folder 456: 8)
      - W-Z, 1990-1996 (Box-folder 456: 9-10)
    - Subject file
      - Arthur Shenfield's collected works, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 457: 1)
      - Best of Wincott Lectures, 1990 (Box-folder 457: 2)
      - Chapter on electricity for deregulation book, Economic Planning Agency, Japanese Government, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 457: 3-4)
      - Possibles, Portuguese/English dictionary, undated (Box-folder 457: 5)
      - Possibles under IEA imprint, 1994-1996 (Box-folder 457: 6)
      - Publications under IEA imprint, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 457: 7)
      - Stock of books at Goron, 1992-1996 (Box-folder 457: 8)
  - Publications With Other Publishers File, 1988-1992
    Includes correspondence, manuscripts and contracts related to the series “IEA Masters of Modern Economics” published by Basil Blackwell Limited, as well as to two books published by Routledge. Arranged alphabetically by title of publication.
    - Adam Smith's Legacy, 1990-1992 (Box-folder 457: 9)
    - "IEA Masters of Modern Economics," Hayek, Buchanan, Friedman
      - General, 1990-1992 (Box-folder 457: 10)
      - Authors' promotion forms, undated (Box-folder 457: 11)
      - Basil Blackwell Limited, 1988-1990 (Box-folder 458: 1)
      - Bibliographic lists, undated (Box-folder 458: 2)
      - Edward Elgar Publishing Limited, 1988 (Box-folder 458: 3)
      - Introductions, 1989-1991 (Box-folder 458: 4)
      - Memoranda of Agreement, 1989 (Box-folder 458: 5)
      - Wheatsheaf Books Limited, 1988 (Box-folder 458: 6)
    - Recent Controversies in Political Economy, 1990-1992 (Box-folder 458: 7)
  - Subject File, 1976-1998
    Includes clippings, correspondence, printed matter, and notes. Arranged alphabetically.
    - Adam Smith Institute, 1987-1995 (Box-folder 459: 1)
    - ARCO British scenarios, 1994 (Box-folder 459: 2)
    - Atlas Economic Research Foundation, 1987-1993 (Box-folder 459: 3-6)
    - Atlas Economic Research Foundation (cont'd.), 1987-1993 (Box-folder 460: 1-2)
    - British Council, 1998 (Box-folder 460: 3)
    - Brittan, Kaldor, Rose, Minford, Walters, Pepper, Burton, Wanell, 1983 (Box-folder 460: 4)
    - Cato Institute, 1989-1996 (Box-folder 460: 5)
    - Centre Forward, MP's group, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 460: 6)
    - Clocks, 1985-1993 (Box-folder 460: 7)
    - Church, economics and socialism, 1983-1988 (Box-folder 460: 8)
    - Disciples group, 1981-1990 (Box-folder 460: 9)
    - EC competition policy, Victoria Curzon Price, 1992 (Box-folder 460: 10)
    - Fraser Institute, 1987-1996 (Box-folder 460: 11)
    - Groom Books, 1993-1995 (Box-folder 460: 12)
    - Independent University, 1976-1983 (Box-folder 461: 1)
    - Institute for Children, 1993-1996 (Box-folder 461: 2-6)
    - Institute for Children (cont'd.), 1993-1996 (Box-folder 462: 1-4)
    - Institute of Humane Studies, 1990-1993 (Box-folder 462: 5-6)
    - Labour think tanks, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 462: 7)
    - Mather, Graham, 1988-1990 (Box-folder 462: 8)
    - Miscellaneous, 1981-1992 (Box-folder 463: 1)
    - Nuclear review, evidence, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 463: 2)
    - Poleconomy, 1995 (Box-folder 463: 3)
    - Refuse and cleaning, 1985, undated (Box-folder 463: 4)
    - Wade, Bruce Naughton, 1995 (Box-folder 463: 5)
  - Office File, 1963-2005
    Scope and content note
    Includes correspondence, memoranda, and clippings related to IEA’s departments, office events, and administrative work. Includes essays and correspondence for the John B. Wood Essay Competition. Arranged alphabetically by format.
    - Articles of Association, 1963 (Box-folder 463: 6)
    - Brochures, 2002, undated (Box-folder 463: 7)
    - Clippings related to IEA, 1988-1992 (Box-folder 463: 8-9)
    - Clippings related to IEA (cont'd.), 1988-1992 (Box-folder 464: 1)
    - Correspondence
      - General
        - 1967 (Box-folder 464: 2)
        - 1988-1993 (Box-folder 464: 3)
        - 1992-2001 (Box-folder 464: 4)
      - Australia, 1987-1995 (Box-folder 464: 5-6)
      - Centre for Policy Studies, 1986-1995 (Box-folder 464: 7-8)
      - Charities Aid Foundation, 1987-1990 (Box-folder 464: 9)
      - Charities Aid Foundation (cont'd.), 1987-1990 (Box-folder 465: 1-2)
      - Confederation of British Industry, 1990-1993 (Box-folder 465: 3)
      - Harris, Ralph, 1964-1970 (Box-folder 465: 4)
      - Heath, Edward, 1964-1970, 2001 (Box-folder 465: 5)
      - IEA Trustees, 1987-1991 (Box-folder 465: 6-8)
      - Institute of Directors, 1986-1991 (Box-folder 466: 1)
      - Main Image LTD, "Lord North Street Tapes,", 1993-1995 (Box-folder 466: 2)
        See Audiovisual Materials for cassette tape, "IEA Pilot," April 1993.
      - Raybould, John, 1992-1997 (Box-folder 466: 3)
    - Interview, Bartley and Anthony Fisher, 1983 (Box-folder 466: 4)
    - John B. Wood Essay Competition
      - Fifth Annual Competition
        - General, 1997 (Box-folder 466: 5)
        - Essays, 1997 (Box-folder 466: 6-7)
        - Rankings, 1997 (Box-folder 466: 8)
      - Sixth Annual Competition
        - Essays, 1998, undated (Box-folder 466: 9)
        - Essays (cont'd.), 1998, undated (Box-folder 467: 1-2)
        - Flyer, undated (Box-folder 467: 3)
        - List of participants, 1988 (Box-folder 467: 4)
        - Memoranda, 1998 (Box-folder 467: 5)
        - Rankings, 1998 (Box-folder 467: 6)
      - Seventh Annual Competition
        - Correspondence, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 467: 7)
        - Flyers, undated (Box-folder 467: 8)
        - Essays, 1999 (Box-folder 467: 9-12)
        - Memoranda, 1999 (Box-folder 467: 13)
        - Rankings, 1999 (Box-folder 468: 1)
      - Eighth Annual Competition
        - Correspondence, 2000 (Box-folder 468: 2)
        - Essays, 2000 (Box-folder 468: 3)
        - Memoranda, 2000 (Box-folder 468: 4)
        - Rankings, 2000 (Box-folder 468: 5)
    - Media log for IEA trustees, 1996 (Box-folder 468: 6)
    - Memoranda
      - General, 1991-1997 (Box-folder 468: 7-8)
      - General director, 1992-1996 (Box-folder 468: 9-10)
      - General director (cont'd.), 1992-1996 (Box-folder 469: 1)
    - Miscellany, 1995-1999, undated (Box-folder 469: 2)
    - Obituaries, 1988-1992 (Box-folder 469: 3-4)
    - Postcards and comics, 1999, undated (Box-folder 469: 5)
    - Resumes, curricula vitae, and autobiographies, 1985-1992, undated (Box-folder 469: 6-7)
    - Subject file
      - Anniversaries
        - Thirtith Anniversary, 1987 (Box-folder 469: 8)
        - Fiftieth Anniversary, 2005 (Box-folder 469: 9)
      - Antony Fisher Biography Project, 1982-2000 (Box-folder 469: 10-11)
      - "Better Off out? The Benefits and Costs of EU Membership,", 1996 (Box-folder 470: 1)
      - Blundell, John, 1994-1997 (Box-folder 470: 2)
      - Building maintenance, 1969-1990 (Box-folder 470: 3-9)
      - Hutty, Malcolm, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 470: 10)
      - Patrons, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 470: 11)
      - Regulation Unit, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 470: 12)
      - Strategy, 1992-1995 (Box-folder 470: 13)
      - Website, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 470: 14)
    - Writings by others
      - Cobin, John M., 1996-1997 (Box-folder 470: 15)
      - Goddard, John and Neill Marshall, 1992 (Box-folder 470: 16)
  - John Blundell File, 1987-2004
    Includes correspondence, memoranda, clippings, and meeting materials related to the activites of John Blundell, who became general director of the IEA in 1993. See also the Atlas Network File and Institute for Humane Studies File, which contain materials from Blundell's time as president of both these organizations.
    - General, 1987-1999 (Box-folder 471: 1)
    - Correspondence
      - General
        - Incoming letters, 1993-1997 (Box-folder 471: 2)
        - Outgoing letters, 1994-1997 (Box-folder 471: 3)
      - Blanchette, Jude, 2004 (Box-folder 471: 4)
      - Rich, Andrea, Laissez Faire Books, 1994-1996 (Box-folder 471: 5)
      - Mkutu, Kennedy, 1998 (Box-folder 471: 6)
    - Day Files
      Includes correspondence, memoranda, agendas, invitations, clippings, and speeches and writings.
      - 1991 (Box-folder 471: 7)
      - 1992 (Box-folder 471: 8)
      - 1993 (Box-folder 471: 9)
      - 1994 (Box-folder 471: 10)
      - 1995
        - January (Box-folder 472: 1)
        - February (Box-folder 472: 2)
        - March (Box-folder 472: 3)
        - April (Box-folder 472: 4)
        - May (Box-folder 472: 5)
        - June (Box-folder 472: 6)
        - July (Box-folder 472: 7)
        - August (Box-folder 472: 8)
        - September (Box-folder 472: 9)
        - October (Box-folder 472: 10)
        - November (Box-folder 472: 11)
        - December (Box-folder 472: 12)
      - 1996
        - January (Box-folder 472: 13)
        - February (Box-folder 472: 14)
        - March (Box-folder 472: 15)
        - April (Box-folder 472: 16-17)
        - April (cont'd.) (Box-folder 473: 1)
        - May (Box-folder 473: 2)
        - June (Box-folder 473: 3-4)
        - July (Box-folder 473: 5)
        - August (Box-folder 473: 6)
        - September (Box-folder 473: 7-8)
        - October (Box-folder 473: 9)
        - November (Box-folder 473: 10)
        - December (Box-folder 474: 1)
      - 1997
        - January (Box-folder 474: 2)
        - February (Box-folder 474: 3)
        - March (Box-folder 474: 4)
        - April (Box-folder 474: 5)
        - May (Box-folder 474: 6)
        - June (Box-folder 474: 7-8)
        - June (cont'd.) (Box-folder 475: 1)
        - July (Box-folder 475: 2-3)
        - August (Box-folder 475: 4)
        - September (Box-folder 475: 5-6)
        - October (Box-folder 475: 7)
        - October (cont'd.) (Box-folder 476: 1-2)
        - November (Box-folder 476: 3-4)
        - December (Box-folder 476: 5-6)
      - 1998
        - January (Box-folder 477: 1-2)
        - February (Box-folder 477: 3-4)
        - March (Box-folder 477: 5-6)
        - March (Box-folder 478: 1-3)
        - April (Box-folder 478: 4-5)
        - May (Box-folder 478: 6-7)
        - May (cont'd.) (Box-folder 479: 1-2)
        - June (Box-folder 479: 3-6)
        - July (Box-folder 479: 7)
        - July (cont'd.) (Box-folder 480: 1)
        - September (Box-folder 480: 2-4)
        - October (Box-folder 480: 5-6)
        - October (cont'd.) (Box-folder 481: 1)
        - November (Box-folder 481: 2-4)
        - December (Box-folder 481: 5-6)
      - 1999
        - January (Box-folder 482: 1-2)
        - February (Box-folder 482: 3-4)
        - March (Box-folder 482: 5-6)
        - March (cont'd.) (Box-folder 483: 1)
        - April (Box-folder 483: 2-3)
        - May (Box-folder 483: 4-7)
        - June (Box-folder 484: 1-3)
        - July (Box-folder 484: 4-6)
        - August (Box-folder 484: 7)
        - September (Box-folder 500: 1-2)
        - October (Box-folder 500: 3-5)
        - November (Box-folder 500: 6-7)
        - December (Box-folder 501: 1)
      - 2000
        - January (Box-folder 501: 2)
        - February (Box-folder 501: 3-4)
        - March (Box-folder 501: 5-6)
        - April (Box-folder 501: 7)
        - May (Box-folder 501: 8)
        - May (cont'd.) (Box-folder 502: 1)
        - June (Box-folder 502: 2-3)
        - July (Box-folder 502: 4-5)
        - August (Box-folder 502: 6)
        - September (Box-folder 502: 7)
        - October (Box-folder 503: 1-2)
        - November (Box-folder 503: 3)
        - December (Box-folder 503: 4)
    - Leaflets, IEA conferences, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 503: 5)
    - Lists of names and contact information, circa 2000 (Box-folder 503: 6)
    - Meeting materials, Charles G. Koch Chartiable Foundation, Board of Trustees, 1992 (Box-folder 503: 7)
    - Personnel file, 2000 (Box-folder 503: 8)
    - Subject file
      - Aims of Industry Free Enterprise Award, 2000 (Box-folder 504: 1)
      - Association Savoir et Developpment Liberal, 1998 (Box-folder 504: 2)
      - Bauer, Peter T., 2000 (Box-folder 504: 3)
      - Conferences and lectures, 1998-2000 (Box-folder 504: 4)
      - DeRugy, Veronique, 1997 (Box-folder 504: 5)
      - Dictionary of Dangerous Words, 1999 (Box-folder 504: 6)
      - Driscoll, Jerry and John Hulsman, 2000 (Box-folder 504: 7)
      - Du Pont, Pete, 1997 (Box-folder 504: 8)
      - Economic Affairs endorsements, 2000 (Box-folder 504: 9)
      - Griswold, Daniel T., 1997 (Box-folder 504: 10)
      - Hotels and dining clubs, 1999, undated (Box-folder 504: 11)
      - Institute for Children, 1995-1997 (Box-folder 504: 12)
      - IEA Finance and General Purposes Committee, 2000 (Box-folder 505: 1)
      - Logos, undated (Box-folder 505: 2)
      - Miscellaneous, 1992-1998, undated (Box-folder 505: 3)
      - Morocco, 1997 (Box-folder 505: 4)
      - Murdoch, Elizabeth, 1999 (Box-folder 505: 5)
      - Seminar, "Protecting the United Kingdom's Streams Through Water Markets,", 2000 (Box-folder 505: 6)
      - Templeton Forum, 2000 (Box-folder 505: 7)
      - Tomorrow Project, 1997 (Box-folder 505: 8)
      - Think tanks, 1998 (Box-folder 505: 9)
      - Website, 1997-1999 (Box-folder 505: 10)
      - Wincott Lectures, 1996 (Box-folder 505: 11)
  - Gerald Frost File, 1993-1999
    Includes correspondence, memoranda, press releases, and speeches and writings related to the activities of Gerald Frost, who was director of IEA's Trade and Development Unit. See also Computer Media.
    - Agenda, Marketing Committee meeting, 1998 (Box-folder 506: 1)
    - Budget, Trade and Development Unit, undated (Box-folder 506: 2)
    - Correspondence
      - General
        - Undated (Box-folder 506: 3)
        - 1997 (Box-folder 506: 4)
        - 1998 (Box-folder 506: 5)
        - 1999 (Box-folder 506: 6)
      - Angell, Ian, 1998 (Box-folder 506: 7)
      - Buckley, Peter J., 1998-1999 (Box-folder 506: 8)
      - Lal, Deepak K., 1997-1998 (Box-folder 506: 9)
      - Minford, Patrick, 1998 (Box-folder 506: 10)
      - Minogue, Kenneth, 1998 (Box-folder 506: 11)
      - O'Grady, Mary, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 506: 12)
      - Wolf, Martin, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 506: 13)
    - Flyer, 1999 (Box-folder 506: 14)
    - IEA working paper, 1997 (Box-folder 506: 15)
    - Lists, 1997 (Box-folder 506: 16)
      Includes address lists and guest lists.
    - Memoranda, 1998 (Box-folder 506: 17)
    - Mission statement, Trade and Development Unit, undated (Box-folder 506: 18)
      See also Computer Media.
    - Notes, 1997-1998, undated (Box-folder 506: 19)
    - Press releases, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 506: 20)
    - Speeches and writings
      - "Don't Sell Our Services Short,", undated (Box-folder 506: 21)
      - "America Awakens to the New Europe,", 1997 (Box-folder 506: 22)
      - "Tories Should Remember Their Principles,", 1997 (Box-folder 506: 23)
    - Subject file
      - Databases, undated (Box-folder 506: 24)
      - Houses and Herbert Hoover, 1993 (Box-folder 506: 25)
      - Stationery, 1997 (Box-folder 506: 26)
    - Writings by others
      - General, 1998 (Box-folder 506: 27)
      - "British Arms Exports After the Cold War,", 1998 (Box-folder 506: 28)
  - Graham Mather File, 1987-1992
    Correspondence relating to activities of Graham Mather, general director of the IEA until 1992. See also Gerald Frost File in the original accession.
    - Correspondence
      - 1987 (Box-folder 507: 1)
      - 1989 (Box-folder 507: 2)
      - 1990 (Box-folder 507: 3)
      - 1991 (Box-folder 507: 4)
      - 1992 (Box-folder 507: 5)
    - IEA guidelines, 1992 (Box-folder 507: 6)
  - Arthur Seldon File, 1976-1998
    Correspondence relating to the activities of Arthur Seldon, who was editorial director of IEA from 1957-1981, editor of Economic Affairs from 1980-1986, and advisory director of publications after 1987. See also Arthur Seldon File in original accession.
    - Correspondence
      - Undated (Box-folder 507: 7)
      - 1976-1978 (Box-folder 507: 8)
      - 1987-1989 (Box-folder 507: 9)
      - 1990-1992 (Box-folder 507: 10)
      - 1993 (Box-folder 507: 11)
      - 1994 (Box-folder 507: 12)
      - 1995 (Box-folder 507: 13)
      - 1996 (Box-folder 507: 14)
      - 1997 (Box-folder 507: 15)
      - 1998 (Box-folder 507: 16)
    - Sevenoaks property file, 1976, 1996, undated (Box-folder 507: 17)
  - Margaret Thatcher File, 1967-2009
    Includes correspondence between British Prime Minister Margaret Thatcher and IEA member Ralph Harris, as well as letters from other British politicians such as Ian Gow.
    - General, 1982, undated (Box-folder 508: 1)
    - Clippings, 1984-2009 (Box-folder 508: 2)
    - Correspondence
      - 1969-1975 (Box-folder 508: 3)
      - 1977 (Box-folder 508: 4)
      - 1978 (Box-folder 508: 5)
      - 1979 (Box-folder 508: 6)
      - 1980 (Box-folder 508: 7)
      - 1981 (Box-folder 508: 8)
      - 1982 (Box-folder 508: 9)
      - 1983 (Box-folder 508: 10)
      - 1988 (Box-folder 508: 11)
      - 1989 (Box-folder 508: 12)